

Abhishek Pawar

Frontend Developer

Career Objective

To pursue a challenging career and be a part of progressive organization that gives a scope to enhance my knowledge and utilize my skills towards the growth of the organization.

Synopsis

 With 2.6 years of experience as a Frontend Developer, I excel in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, React.js, and Next.js. I prioritize responsive design, crossbrowser compatibility, and have a keen eye for UI/UX.

My Contact

☑ abhishekpwr944@gmail.comℚ 7276343346

-

Pimple Saudagar,Pune,Maharashtra

www.linkedin.com/in/abhishek-ap7

https://my-portfolio-two-omega-14.vercel.app/

Primary Skill

- · HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript,
- Typescript, AJAX, JQuery, React Js,
- Next Js, Redux Js, Node Js,
- Express Js, MongoDB, MySQL,
- · React Dev Tool, Redux Dev Tool,
- GIT, Material UI.

Secondary Skill

- Tailwind CSS
- React Native

Education Background

- Master Of Computer Science (MCS)
 Pune University
 Completed in 2020
- Bachelor Of Computer Science (BCS)
 Pune University
 Completed in 2018
- HSC

Pune Board

Completed in 2013

SSC
 Pune Board
 Completed in 2011

Professional Experience

Intelliconnect Technologies | Frontend Developer

20/02/2023 - 19/08/2023

Key responsibilities:

- Develop responsive websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, React Js, Next Js.
- Work with REST API's.
- Work with Tech leads on scoping and planning effort estimation and timeline for development.

Plus 91 Technologies Pvt Ltd | Frontend Developer

21/03/2022 - 7/11/2022

Key responsibilities:

- Develop responsive websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, React Js.
- Work with REST API's.
- Work with Tech leads on scoping and planning effort estimation and timeline for development.

Spwebconnect Solutions | Trainee Software Developer

14th May 2021 - 21st March 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Client: thecooldaddy
- Designed(http://thecooldaddy.com)(responsive pages using html5, css3, JQuery,Js).
- Work with Tech leads on scoping and planning effort estimation and timeline for development.

Gatitaa Technology | Php Intern

31st October 2020 - 25th February 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Client: Saturotechnologies
- Designed(https://saturotech.com/netsuite-erp.php) (responsive pages using html5, css3, JQuery,Js).
- Work with Tech leads on scoping and planning effort estimation and timeline for development.

Certification Course

• MERN Stack